<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Christian Tan</title>
    <link>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Christian Tan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Covid-19 Data Visualization</title>
      <link>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/project-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/project-4/</guid>
      <description>Background:
The main goal for this project was to create a Dashboard Visualization for important data from the Covid-19 pandemic using Excel, SQL, and Tableau. The size of the spreadsheet was around 90,000 lines of data. Skills that were used included: Joins, CTE&amp;rsquo;s, Temp Tables, Windows Functions, Aggregate Functions, Creating Views, Converting Data Types, and Creating Visualizations/Dashboards in Tableau.
The data is from https://ourworldindata.org/covid-deaths.
Part 1: First, I downloaded the data into excel spreadsheets to do some initial cleaning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cyclistic - How a Bike-Share Company Can Navigate Speedy Success</title>
      <link>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents   Mission Statement and Preliminary Information
  Data Preparation and Exploration
  Data Processing
  Data Analyzing
  Share and Conclusion
  Mission Statement: The bike sharing company wants to analyze their users’ data to find the main differences between two certain types of users, the “casual” who pays for each ride and the “annual” member who pays a yearly subscription for the service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The NBA 3-Point Revolution - The Way For NBA Teams to Win More Games</title>
      <link>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents
  Project Description
  Data Preparation and Exploration
   2.1 Data information 2.2 Brief Exploration 2.3 Data Transformations  Modeling   3.1 Bar Chart 3.2 Plot Chart 3.3 Density Plot Chart 3.4 Significant/Insignificant Coefficients 3.5 Predictive Performance 3.6 Accuracy, Recall, Precision   Results and Discussion
  Conclusion
  1. Project Description   Conventionally, in the sport of basketball there are defined player positions with standard body profiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bellabeat - 3 Ways a Wellness Tech Company Can Play It Smart</title>
      <link>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ctan1237.github.io/Christian_Portfolio/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents   Mission Statement and Preliminary Information
  Data Preparation and Exploration
  Data Processing
  Data Analyzing
  Share and Conclusion
  The Mission Statement: Bellabeat, a high-tech manufacturer of health-focused products for women, wants to analyze their smart device fitness data. This could help unlock new growth opportunities for the company. The goal is to focus on one of Bellabeat’s products and analyze smart device data to gain insight into how consumers are using their smart devices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
